Hey, hey, what are you doing?
ほらほら、何してるの?
where are you going
どこへ行こうとしてる
of?
の?
I'm just inside.
ちょっと 中入りだよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、 そうなんだ
Ride both here.
ここで両方乗れ
yes.
はい
Have you escaped yet?
まだ逃げとったんか?
It's like he hasn't reflected on it much.
あんま反省してないみたいなの
I thought I should run away.
逃げれば思った
Are you reflecting?
反省してるの?
I am doing.
してます
I'm going to get an office.
事務所取れて行くぞ
yes.
はい
It's kind of growing.
なんか成長してますね
It's growing.
成長してるよ
This is an E cup after all.
やっぱりEカップになってる、これ
It's not D.
Dじゃないよ
It's about as big as E.
Eぐらい大きくなってるから
E cup from today.
今日からEカップね
Got it?
分かった?
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
This one has a different bulge.
膨らみが違うよ、これ
Everyone should see this.
みんな見ちゃう、これ
All men will see this.
男みんな見るよ、これ
Everyone is looking at my boobs on the train.
電車でみんな見てるよ、おっぱい
Doesn't it feel natural?
自然感じない?
Don't you feel like that?
そんな気しない?
I feel like I'm being watched.
なんか見られてるなぁ、みたいな
Maybe everyone is looking at Ligacha's boobs.
多分みんなリガチャのおっぱい見てるよ、
this.
これ
This is my precious pair of pants.
大事なパンツ入って、これ
Where did you buy this?
どこで買っちゃったの、これ
It's so naughty.
エッチエッチだよ
Naughty.
エッチ
That's amazing.
すごいね
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
This is really big.
めっちゃおっきいよ、これ
Amazing, amazing.
すごい、すごい
Can I pinch your finger for a moment?
ちょっと指挟んでいい?
This is amazing.
すごいよ、これ
I feel the pressure,
圧力を感じるよ、
this.
これ
This is what happens because you don't pay back the money properly.
ちゃん とお金返さないから、こんなことになっちゃうんだよ
That's right.
そうだよね
Haven't you returned it yet?
まだ返さなかった?
I forgot to make it in time.
間に合い忘れました
That's all there is to it.
そればっかりじゃん
Are you planning on giving it back?
返す気あんの?
Are you willing to give it back?
返す気ある?
yes.
はい
be?
ある?
Could you please look at the camera properly?
ちゃんとカメラ見ていってもらえない?
there is.
あります
Did you want to be sorry today?
今日申し訳されたかったの?
Shall we have a lot of sex?
いっぱい仲出しちゃおうか
Shall we have sex?
仲出しちゃおうか
Shall we have a baby?
子作りしちゃおうか
Also.
また
Should I take it down again?
もう一回下ろす?
What should I do?
どうする?
What should I do if I can do it?
出来ちゃったらどうしよっか
Shall I take off my top shirt?
上のシャツ脱いちゃおうか
Which shirt is this?
これどこのシャツ?
Let's meet up and go home.
あとは出会い帰ろうかな
On the way back from the encounter.
出会い帰りに
hey.
ね
Now, raise your hands.
さあ、両手上げて
behind your head.
頭後ろで
I also check my armpit hair, right?
脇毛チェックもしちゃうのね、これね
Shall we go on the balcony?
ベランダでいっちゃおうか
If you speak out loud, you'll be found out.
声出たらバレちゃうよ
To the toilet.
ご便所さんに
Did you just do it on the balcony?
さっきベランダでやろっか
Let's do it on the balcony.
ベランダでやろっか
Let's go on the balcony, okay?
ベランダでいこっか、そっか
Chain time.
チェーンの時間
I really do it.
めっちゃやるのに
I'll do it like this.
こうやるのに
Eurakegas.
ユーラケガス
Let me show you.
見せまして
You'll be seen.
見られちゃうね
Squeakiness.
きしさ
It's cute and it's nice to want to do it.
かわいいし、したいのもいいし
Manpo's tightness is also nice.
マンポのしもりもいいじゃん
But I won't get my money back.
でもお金は返さないもんな
It's a bag from hell.
地獄のバッグだね
Al-chan.
アルちゃん
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Yes, it feels good.
はい、気持ちいいです
Get some alcohol, I have a dick.
お酒入れて、俺のチンコあるからな
I'll put it in for you after drinking.
お酒の後、俺が入れてやるわ
Is it sake?
お酒、せいろいっすか
Can you open your pussy yourself?
自分でおまんこ開ける?
Can you make an ahegao face?
アヘ顔できる?
Ah...
アヘ...
The whites of the eyes, like the whites of the eyes.
白目、白目みたいな
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Try doing it while saying you're in bed.
ベッドですって言いながらやってみて
It's a bed.
ベッドです
I'll listen to anything good.
なんでもよいこと聞きます
What should I do next?
次何しよっか?
Will you be with me next time?
次俺と一緒か?
What should I do?
どうする?
Did you think you would?
するんだって思ったっけ?
yes.
はい
Stand in front of me and raise your butt.
手 前について、お尻つきあげて
That's amazing, really.
すごいね、本当
It's so hot.
めちゃくちゃイッチだね
It's so tight, pussy
プニプニだね、おまんこ
too.
も
I have to start cleaning up the alcohol.
お 酒のお掃除からしなきゃ
I have to say thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでしたって言わなきゃ
Thank you for the meal.
ごちそうさまでした
Shall we go home?
帰ろうか
Well then
じゃあ
Na.
な
Come here tomorrow too.
明 日もこっち来い
Got it?
分かった?
I think I can escape.
逃げられると思うんだよ
I'll be living here from today onwards.
今日からここに住むことになるから
Because I can't go home anymore.
もう 家帰れないから
Did you understand?
分 かった?
After all.
何しろ
It's up here.
ここに上だよな
I'll come back later.
あとで戻ってくるから
Come properly.
ちゃんと来い